Alright today, great one for you.
This is a nice one for dinner, it's stuffed shrimp, we're going to be using crab.
Now you can go out and buy lump crab meat, which I'll talk about later, or you can have some of these beautiful King crab legs that I had leftover, and make your own crab meat which I'm going to do today because I think I saw crab, lumped crab meat at like twenty dollars a pound .
Where, this is a lot cheaper, not that much if you think about it but definitely about ten dollars a pound as opposed to twenty dollars a pound already done for you.
Alright, so what are we going to do?
We're going to get some great shrimp.
Let me talk about stuffed shrimp first of all.
What I know about it is that it's amazing.
It's taking some crab meat and mixing it with, making a nice stuffing and stuffing your shrimp with it.
Putting it in your oven, it just cooks golden brown and comes out yummy, yummy, yummy and it's a great dinner.
A great way to impress the girls, guys.